{
    "id": "171e6d65252244f9969487dd542fe163",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ……………….. her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "takes after",
                "takes on",
                "takes away"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The militants took the captives ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The opposition leader insisted that the minister should ………………… his remarks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take after",
                "take back",
                "take down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ....................... what I say.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take down",
                "take off",
                "take out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Activists forced the shop to ………………….. their neon sign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take off",
                "take down",
                "take back"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t take him ………………. an idiot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "after",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were ....................... by a con artist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken out",
                "taken in",
                "taken for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindus take their shoes ………………… before entering a house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "As I was not feeling well, I decided to take a day …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid you have ..................... too much responsibility.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken out",
                "taken on",
                "taken off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}